A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 2, Accession 2017:058 FA1393
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1978-2011; 1
  - Royal Oak Foundation - Seeds for Thought Lecture, 2002-2011 (Box 79, Folder 585)
  - St. Vladimir's Orthodox Theological Seminary, 1991-1996 (Box 28, Folder 194)
  - School of Oriental and African Studies (University of London) - The China Quarterly, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 195)
  - The Seamen's Church Institute - ITC Senior Port Missioner Program, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 196)
  - Smithsonian Institution - Photography Initiative, 2006-2008 (Box 79, Folder 586)
  - Society for Values in Education - Teaching Workshops, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 197-198)
  - Society of Biblical Literature, 1994-1998 (Box 29, Folder 199)
  - South Africa Free Elections Fund (SAFE), 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 200)
  - South Street Seaport Museum - James Buttersworth Catalog, 1993-1997 (Box 29, Folder 201)
  - Southeast Asia Art Foundation - Southeast Asian Art Photographic Archives, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 202)
  - Southwestern University - Research Trip to Tibet, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 203)
  - Speed Art Museum - Collaboration with University of Kentucky Art Museum (ACE), 2000-2006 (Box 79, Folder 587)
  - Spelman College Museum of Fine Arts - Hale Woodruff and the Academy, 2005-2007 (Box 80, Folder 588)
  - Stanford University - Dialogue, Research, and Exchange with North Korea, 2004-2007 (Box 80, Folder 589)
  - Stanford University - Disarmament and Peace on the Korean Peninsula, 2007-2010 (Box 80, Folder 590)
  - Stanford University - Southeast Asia Initiative, 1998-2003 (Box 80, Folder 591)
  - Stonington Historical Society, Inc. - Richard Woolworth Library, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 204)
  - The Synod of the Northeast of the Presbyterian Church - Cluster Ministries in Upstate New York, 1991-1997 (Box 29, Folder 205)
  - Rabbi Marc H. Tanenbaum Foundation - "Abraham's Children", 1995-1998 (Box 29, Folder 206)
  - Teach for America, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 207)
  - Temple of Understanding - International Interfaith Outreach, 1994-1999 (Box 30, Folder 208-209)
    - We Are One - Produced by the Temple of Understanding by Galen Films Inc., undated; VHS (Box T1)
  - Tibet House, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 210)
  - Toledo Museum of Art - American Glass Collection (Glass Pavilion), 2005-2009 (Box 80, Folder 592)
  - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review - Chairman's Award, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 211)
  - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review - Expand and Develop Subscriber Base, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 212)
  - The Trust for Museum Exhibitions - Peale Legacy, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 213, Box 31, Folder 214)
  - Tweed Museum of Art - Gilbert David Munger, 2001-2011 (Box 80, Folder 593)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Annex to Henry R. Luce Chapel at Payap University, 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 215)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Archives, 1993-1996 (Box 31, Folder 216)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - China Studies Program at De La Salle University, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 217)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Faculty Exchange with ASIANetwork, 1994-1998 (Box 31, Folder 218)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Radio Production Studio - St. Paul College, Philippines, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 219)
  - United States Committee for UNICEF - United Nation's Art Collection, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 220)
  - University of Alaska Museum, 2001-2007 (Box 81, Folder 594-595)
  - University of the Arts - National Arts Journalism Program (NAJP) Journalism Conference, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 596)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Symposium on Chinese Art History, 1993-1997 (Box 32, Folder 221)
  - University of California, Berkeley and Fudan University - China's Quest for Modernization Conference and Publication, 1991-1995 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - University of California, San Diego - Korea-Pacific Program, 1989-1996 (Box 32, Folder 223)
  - University of Denver - Robert Yegge Student Center, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 224)
  - The University of Hong Kong - Church and State Relations in the 21st Century, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 225)
  - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign - Take the Lead Program, 1990-1995 (Box 32, Folder 226)
  - University of Maryland Baltimore County - American-East Asian Relations Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 32, Folder 227)
  - University of Michigan - Chinese Women's Studies, 2001-2006 (Box 81, Folder 597)
  - University of Michigan - Chinese Women's Studies (Box 81, Folder 597)
  - University of Michigan - Scholarly Exchange with Burma, 2003-2007 (Box 81, Folder 598)
  - University of Michigan Museum of Art - Betye Saar: Fragmentation, Photography and the Time in Between, 2001-2007 (Box 81, Folder 599)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Chinese Library Professionals, 2002-2006 (Box 82, Folder 600)
  - University of San Francisco - Institute for Chinese-Western Cultural History, 1988-1996 (Box 32, Folder 228)
  - University of San Francisco (Ricci Institute) - Christianity in China, 2003-2006 (Box 82, Folder 601)
  - University of Washington - SEASSI, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 229)
  - University Settlement - Bilingual Teachers Program, 1993-1997 (Box 33, Folder 230)
  - Unrepresented Nations and Peoples Organization - United Nations, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 231)
  - Valparaiso University, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 232)
  - Vanderbilt University (Divinity School) - Degree Program in Theology and Sacred Music, 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 233)
  - Vassar College - Cinema, Literacy, and Culture Extension, 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 234)
  - VIA (Volunteers in Asia) - Volunteer Program, 1995-2005 (Box 82, Folder 602)
  - Walker Art Center, 2003-2005 (Box 82, Folder 603-604)
  - Walker Art Center - Kara Walker: My Lover, My Master, My Enemy, 2006-2008 (Box 82, Folder 605)
  - Warner House Association - Richness and Color in the Warner House, 2005-2010 (Box 83, Folder 606)
  - The Washington Center - Minority Leaders Fellowship Program (Renewal), 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 235-236)
  - Washington University - Realms of Freedom in the Modern Chinese World, 1999-2004 (Box 83, Folder 607)
  - Wesley Theological Seminary - Center for the Arts and Religion, 1997-2000 (Box 83, Folder 608-610)
  - Wesley Theological Seminary - The Sacrament of Serpent Handling, 2004-2005 (Box 83, Folder 611)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Kienholz: A Retrospective, 1995-1998 (Box 34, Folder 237)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Oscar Bluemner, 2004-2006 (Box 83, Folder 612)
  - Williams College - Curricular Initiative for Renewable Energy and Resource Sustainability, 2005-2011 (Box 84, Folder 613-614)
  - The Wilson Center, 1988-1997 (Box 34, Folder 238-239)
  - Winterthur Museum - American Arts Decorative Professorship, 2001-2011 (Box 84, Folder 615)
  - Winterthur Museum - Series of Changing Exhibits, 1993-1998 (Box 34, Folder 240-241)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation - Interdisciplinary Doctoral Education, 2003-2006 (Box 84, Folder 616)
  - World Monuments Fund - Preah Khan Temple, Angkor Cambodia, 2009-2011 (Box 84, Folder 617)
  - World Steward, 2004-2010 (Box 84, Folder 618)
  - Yale-China Association - Teaching English in China (Renewal), 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 242)
  - Yale University - Early Christianity in Rome Research Trip, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 243)
  - Yale University - Pierson College, 2004-2011 (Box 84, Folder 619)
  - Yale University (Department of History of Art) - Study of Pre-Modern China Seminar, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 244)
  - Yale University (School of Architecture) - Timothy Lenahan Memorial Lectures, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 245)
  - Yale University Art Gallery - Thomas Eakings Rowing Pictures, 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 246)
  - Yenching Graduate Institute - T.C. Chao Conference, 2004-2011 (Box 84, Folder 620)
  - Yenching Graduate Institute - T.C. Chao Publications, 2005-2011 (Box 84, Folder 621)
  - YWCA of the City of New York - Flushing Branch, 1994-1996 (Box 35, Folder 247)
- Professorship Files, 1967-2004; 2
  - Amherst College - Comparative Religious Ethics, 1978-1993 (Box 35, Folder 248-249)
  - Bard College - Freedom of Inquiry and Expression, 1988-2004 (Box 35, Folder 250-251)
  - Brown University, 1990-1993 (Box 36, Folder 252-255)
    Scope and Contents
    Transnational Organization and Comparative Study of Development files.
  - Brown University - Three Year Extension - Transnational Organization, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 256-257)
  - California Institute of Technology - Law and Social Change in the Technological Society, 1967-1982 (Box 37, Folder 258-260)
  - Carleton College - Creative Arts, 1973-1987 (Box 38, Folder 261-262)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Technology and Social Change, 1990-1997 (Box 38, Folder 263-265)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Aging, Health and Society, 1984-1993 (Box 38, Folder 266-267, Box 39, Folder 268-270)
  - Claremont McKenna College, 1982-1993 (Box 39, Folder 271-272)
  - Clark University - Cultural Identity and Global Processes, 1990-2004 (Box 39, Folder 273-274)
  - College of the Holy Cross - Religion, Economic Development and Social Justice, 1986-1999 (Box 40, Folder 275-277)
  - Columbia University - International Political Economy, 1979-1994 (Box 40, Folder 278-280)
  - Cornell University - Science and Society, 1969-1999 (Box 40, Folder 281-282, Box 41, Folder 283-286)
  - Cornell University - Printed Matter, 1968-1976 (Box 41, Folder 287-288)
  - Dartmouth College - Environmental Studies and Policy, 1969-2002 (Box 42, Folder 289-291)
  - Duke University - Democracy, Liberty and the Market Economy, 1983-1994 (Box 42, Folder 292-295)
  - Emory University, 1969-2004 (Box 43, Folder 296-303)
    Humanities and Comparative Studies, Law and the Behavioral Sciences files.
  - Emory University (Renewal), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 304)
  - Emory University - Financial Statements, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 305)
    Restricted - financial material.
  - Emory University - Articles re: Robitscher, 1971-1976 (Box 44, Folder 306)
  - Emory University - Jonas Robitscher's Lectures, 1968-1977 (Box 44, Folder 307)
  - Emory University - Jonas Robitscher's Writings, 1968-1981 (Box 44, Folder 308)
  - Emory University - Printed Matter, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 309)
  - Grinnell College - Nations and the Global Environment, 1989-1994 (Box 44, Folder 310-311)
  - Grinnell College (Renewal), 1994-1999 (Box 45, Folder 312-313)
  - Hampshire College - Food, Resources and International Policy, 1967-1995 (Box 45, Folder 314-317, Box 46, Folder 318)
  - Hampshire College (Renewal), 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 319)
  - Hampshire College - Law Program, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 320)
  - Harvard University - Business, Ethics and Public Policy, 1977-1987 (Box 46, Folder 321-324)
  - Harvard University - Luce Film Committee, 1978-1993 (Box 47, Folder 325)
  - Harvard University - Professorship in Film Studies, 1971-1978 (Box 47, Folder 326-328)
  - Harvard University - Renewal Proposal, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 329)
  - Haverford College - Ethics and the Professions, 1976-1988 (Box 47, Folder 330-332)
  - Institute for Advanced Study - Study of Science as a Social Institution, 1991-1997 (Box 48, Folder 333)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Science and Writing, 1980-1987 (Box 48, Folder 334-335)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Professorship Report, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 336)
  - Kenyon College - Art and Politics, 1987-1992 (Box 48, Folder 337)
  - Kenyon College (Renewal), 1993-2002 (Box 48, Folder 338-339)
  - Lehigh University - Cognitive Robotics and the Philosophy of Knowledge, 1986-1993 (Box 49, Folder 340-341)
  - Lehigh University (Renewal), 1994-1999 (Box 49, Folder 342)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1962-1993 (Box 49, Folder 343-345, Box 50, Folder 346)
    International Cooperation and Global Stability, Environment and Public Policy files.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) (Renewal), 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 347)
  - Mount Holyoke College - Cosmology, 1972-1993 (Box 50, Folder 348-350)
  - New York University - Architecture, Urbanism and History, 1983-1992 (Box 50, Folder 351-352)
  - New York University - Irving Kristol's Writings, 1973-1994 (Box 50, Folder 353-354)
  - New York University - Irving Kristol (Renewal), 1974-1995 (Box 51, Folder 355)
  - New York University - Professorship of Urban Values, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 356)
  - New York University (Renewal), 1993 (Box 51, Folder 357)
  - Northwestern University - American Culture and Public Policy, 1978-1988 (Box 51, Folder 358-360)
  - Northwestern University - Report, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 361)
- United States-China Cooperative Research Program, 1975-2010; 3
  The United States-China Cooperative Research Program was initiated in 1998. It's aim was to encourage sustained joint research by American and Chinese scholars on significant topics in the humanities and social sciences to improve understanding of China and US-China relations. The cooperative research projects typically involved two or more collaborators on both the Chinese and American sides, working together over a three-year period.
  - Brandeis University - China's Second Transition: The Economics of Industrial Innovation, 1995-2005 (Box 51, Folder 362)
  - California State University, Stanislaus - Human Evolution in the Paleolithic of Southern China, 1998-2006 (Box 52, Folder 363)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Impact of China's Socioeconomic Reform Policies in Rural Tibet, 1996-2005 (Box 52, Folder 364)
  - Columbia University - Contract in Chinese Economic Culture, 1993-2005 (Box 52, Folder 365)
  - Columbia University - Political Culture in China, Taiwan, and Hong Kong, 1991-2005 (Box 52, Folder 366)
  - Columbia University - The Family in Rural China, 1988-2005 (Box 52, Folder 367)
  - Cornell University - Buddhism and Popular Religion of the Bai People, 1994-2010 (Box 52, Folder 368)
  - Cornell University - Business, Culture, and the State in China 1840-1949, 1991-2005 (Box 53, Folder 369)
  - Dartmouth College - Newly Excavated Chinese Manuscripts, 1997-2005 (Box 53, Folder 370-371)
  - Duke University - Modern and Contemporary Chinese Popular Culture, 1997-2005 (Box 53, Folder 372)
  - Harvard University - Archaeological Investigation of Sharing Civilization, 1991-2005 (Box 53, Folder 373-374)
  - Harvard University - Food Consumption Patterns in Northern China, 1993-2005 (Box 54, Folder 375)
  - Harvard University - State, Society, and the Changing Rural Community, 1988-2005 (Box 54, Folder 376)
  - Northern Illinois University - Origins and Spread of Tai Irrigated Rice Technology in Southern China, 1998-2006 (Box 54, Folder 377)
  - Northwestern University - Merit, Opulence, and the Buddhist Network of Wealth, 1998-2006 (Box 54, Folder 378)
  - Ohio State University - Political Legal Reforms in China, 1994-2005 (Box 54, Folder 379-380)
  - Pacific Lutheran University - The Clan Elder, the Entrepreneur, and the Cadre, 1998-2006 (Box 55, Folder 381)
  - Rutgers University - Investigation of the Boundary between Wu and Jiang-Hwai Dialects, 1998-2006 (Box 55, Folder 382-383)
  - Stanford University - Rural Poverty, Finance and Investments, and Poverty Policies in China, 1995-2002 (Box 55, Folder 384)
  - Stanford University - Workers and Wives: Migration and Labor in Sichuan, 1993-2005 (Box 55, Folder 385)
  - Stanford University - Taiwan and Fukien - A Comparative Ethnographic Survey, 1988-2005 (Box 56, Folder 386)
  - University of Akron - Urbanization from Below, 1993-2005 (Box 56, Folder 387-388)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Productivity and Reform in China's Industrial Economy, 1989-2005 (Box 56, Folder 389-390)
  - University of Washington - Infant Survival in Yunnan, 1993-2005 (Box 56, Folder 391-392)
  - University of Washington - Internal Migration in China: The Hukou System, 1997-2010 (Box 57, Folder 393)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - The Flora of China, 1996-2005 (Box 57, Folder 394)
  - Yale University - Development of Complex Societies in China, 1997-2010 (Box 57, Folder 395-396)
  - Yale University - The Silk Road Project, 1995-2005 (Box 57, Folder 397)
  - Proposals (Volume I), 1998 (Box 57)
    California State University, Stanislaus; Clark University; Columbia University; Duke University; George Washington University; Harvard University; Northern Illinois University
  - Proposals (Volume II), 1998 (Box 58)
    Northwestern University; Pacific Lutheran University; Rice University; Salem State College; State University College of Buffalo; State University of New Jersey, Rutgers
  - Proposals (Volume III), 1998 (Box 58)
    University of California, Berkeley; University of California, Irvine; University of California, Los Angeles; University of California, Santa Barbara; University of Chicago; University of Colorado
  - Proposals (Volume IV), 1998 (Box 58)
    University of Illinois at Chicago; University of Massachusetts, Amherst; University of Massachusetts, Lowell; University of Michigan; University of Oregon; University of Pittsburgh; University of Wisconsin-Parkside
  - Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars, 1975-1991 (Box 59, Folder 398)
  - Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars - Mailing Materials, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 399)
  - Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars - Responses to Questionnaire, 2008 and undated (Box 59, Folder 400)
  - Grant Competition, 1998; 1
    - Advisors, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 401)
    - Advisor Comments, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 402)
      Restricted - personnel material.
    - Guidelines, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 403)
    - Program Announcement, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 404)
    - Recommendation for Grants, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 405)
      Grant summaries sent to the Board of Directors for review.
  - Grant Competition, 1997; 2
    - Advisor - Benjamin Elman, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 406)
    - Advisor - Thomas R. Gottschang, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 407)
    - Advisor - Anne Thurston, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 408)
    - Advisor - Lyman Van Slyke, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 409)
    - Advisor - Martin Whyte, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 410)
    - Guidelines, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 411)
    - Interested, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 412)
    - Lists and Notes, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 413)
    - Program Announcement, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 414)
    - Proposals, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 415)
    - Recommendations for Grants, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 416)
    - Rejection Letters, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 417)
    - Reviewer Comments, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 418)
  - Grant Competition, 1996; 3
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 419)
    - Guidelines, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 420)
    - Lists and Notes, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 421)
    - Henry Luce Memo - Suggestions for Grants, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 422)
      A memo from the Board of Directors to Henry Luce III detailing projects they recommend funding, a list of grant reviewers, and a short summary of program goals for the year.
    - Reviewer Comments, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 423)
    - Reviewer Files - Steven Levine, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 424)
    - Reviewer Files - Thomas G. Rawski, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 425)
    - Reviewer Files - Lyman Van Slyke, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 426)
    - Reviewer Files - Andrew Walder, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 427)
    - Evaluation Sheets, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 427)
  - Grant Competition, 1995; 4
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 428)
    - Guidelines, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 429)
    - Henry Luce Memo - Suggestions for Grants, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 430)
    - Interested, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 431)
    - Lists and Notes, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 432)
    - Program Announcement, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 433)
    - Reviewers, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 434)
    - Reviewer Comments, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 435)
  - Grant Competition, 1994; 5
    - Guidelines, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 436)
    - Henry Luce Memo - Suggestions for Grants, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 437)
    - Lists and Notes, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 438)
    - Program Announcement, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 439)
    - Recommendations for Grants, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 440)
    - Rejection Letters, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 441)
    - Reviewers, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 442)
    - Reviewer Comments, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 443)
  - Grant Competition, 1993; 6
    - Awards, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 444)
    - Guidelines, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 445-447)
    - Henry Luce Memo - Suggestions for Grants, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 448)
    - Interested, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 449)
    - Lists and Notes, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 450)
    - Proposals Received, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 451)
    - Rejection Letters, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 452)
    - Reviewers, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 453)
    - Reviewer Comments, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 454-455)
  - Grant Competition, 1992; 7
    - Guidelines, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 456)
    - Program Liaisons, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 457)
    - Proposal to Board, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 458)
  - Grant Competition, 1991; 8
    - Program Announcement, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 459)
    - Resumption, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 460)
    - Reviewers, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 461)
    - Reviewer Comments, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 462)
  - Grant Competition, 1989; 9
    - Awards, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 463)
    - Interested, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 464)
    - Public Relations Release, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 465)
    - Proposals Received, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 466)
    - Reviewers, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 467)
  - Grant Competition, 1988; 10
    - Advisors, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 468)
    - Awards, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 469)
    - Reviewers, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 470)
    - Proposals, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 471)
  - Grant Competition, 1987; 11
    - Proposals, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 472)
  - Awards - All Years, 1988-1998 (Box 64, Folder 473)
  - Clemenger Report, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 474-475)
  - Early Research, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 476)
  - Evaluation, 1991-1997 (Box 64, Folder 477)
  - Evaluation Preparation, 1996-1997 (Box 65, Folder 478)
  - PRC Restrictions on Survey Research, 1991-1997 (Box 65, Folder 479)
  - Program Liaisons, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 480)
  - Questionnaire - American Scholars, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 481)
  - Questionnaire - Chinese Scholars, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 482)
  - Review Questionnaires and Reports, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 483-484)
  - T. E. Lautz - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 65, Folder 485)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Columbia University, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 486)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Cornell University, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 487)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Harvard University, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 488)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Michigan State University, 1990-1993 (Box 66, Folder 489)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Princeton University, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 490)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Stanford University, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 491)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of California, Berkeley, 1986-1993 (Box 66, Folder 492)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of California, Los Angeles, 1988-1993 (Box 66, Folder 493)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of California, San Diego, 1988-1993 (Box 66, Folder 494)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Chicago, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 495)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Michigan, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 496)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Pennsylvania, 1989-1991 (Box 66, Folder 497)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Pittsburgh, 1986-1992 (Box 66, Folder 498)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Southern California, 1988-1991 (Box 66, Folder 499)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Washington, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 500)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - University of Wisconsin, Madison, 1988-1991 (Box 66, Folder 501)
  - T. E. Lautz Correspondence - Yale University, 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 502)
- Asset Management and Financial Files, 1986-1990; 4 (Box 85)